(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION INTENDED FOR VIEWERS
WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
THE SPORT-GASM FESTIVAL
SURPRISE EJACULATION
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, PLACES,
LAWS AND NAMES ARE PURELY FICTIONAL.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THE WORK
CONTAINS SOME EXTREME LANGUAGE.
Teacher!
All of us XXX shall respect XXXship,
cumpletely display...
the fruits of our training,
to fight sexfully and boldly until climax.
To crush the Perverted Ordinance,
we need to get information
on Fumino Kotoyose...
by infiltrating
the FS student council room.
For her sake...
and for my belly's sake...
I have to delete the FS records.
And now,
we will begin Minotsuki Academy's
Sport-gasm Festival.
THE SPORT-GASM FESTIVAL
SURPRISE EJACULATION
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
The sport-gasm festival has finally begun!
The live commentary is
brought to you by announcer Chino,
the girl who can take in all.
And our analyst is this man.
Famous for
"There's Nothing That Isn't in My Data,"
Shu Nakamura-san.
A pleasure to be here.
Nakamura-san, what are the highlights
of this tournament?
That is not in my data.
You over there!
Following dress code, you must wear
perverted swimsuit at sport-gasm festival.
What's with that chastity belt?
Follow the "perv-code" properly.
If you don't change, you will be punished.
Hmph.
Tsk.
I was trying to avoid lewd sex,
but it can't be helped.
Nanase, take it off.
You have the key.
Alright.
Jun is such a baby.
More importantly, how is the plan?
Yeah, I anticipated this situation
and prepared the TAE.
This is it.
With this, I can extract FS's data.
Put it in for me, Nanase.
M-Me?
There's no way I can
put something like this in myself.
Alright. Good grief.
Only look at the butt, okay?
Don't look at the front.
Hurry up and show me your ass.
Here I go!
Do it!
Aaaah!
Are you an assertive AV actor?
Amazing. Will it fit inside me as well?
It's impossible for a loli.
I'm not a loli.
Ikuko, you're slacking off
on security again.
But I was searching for my destiny dick.
Security and dick, which is more important?
Dick.
Ugh...
Dick is important too, but...
See.
If I have the ultimate dick,
I can make half of humanity happy!
It's the first step towards
world peace, right, Touka-chan?
I suppose so.
The first event is the 100-meter dash.
All participating athletes, please gather
at the entrance gate named "Earth."
Huh?
It's a more normal event
than I thought.
Not really.
Big ball hoarding, big ball rolling,
big pole toppling.
I have a bad feeling about this.
True.
Depending on the event,
there are also erotic contests.
I knew it.
The main event at the end is...
the Seiran Grand Orgy.
The Seiran Grand Orgy?
Yeah. XXX dance, get-pregnant-now mixer...
While dancing to the perverted dance,
the entire student body will have
a huge XXX.
This is the worst.
How did you get through it last year?
I just kept a Legendary XXX face
and no one came near me.
What about Wata-chan?
Umm...
I had a terrible time.
The next event is the girls' big ball toss.
Participating students,
please move to the big entrance gate.
Oh.
It's us.
Let's win this.
Let's do our best.
Right.
I will now explain the event.
Huh?
The big ball hoarding is...
a big erotic contest to see who
can gather the most balls in their pussy.
Huh?
Tsk.
It's starting.
If this keeps up, Nanase-san will...
I can't fit in any more balls.
Asane-chan?
Hurry up, to the nurse's office!
Huh?
Oh, it's you.
Are you lost?
Huh?
Leave it to big sister.
The child seating is right this way.
Eeeh!
Not again this year!
Is that what she goes through
all the time?
Well, with this, Asane and Wata-chan...
has successfully escaped.
W-What should I do?
Huh?
The Legendary XXX Bitch?
I've heard that her XXX
leads to the outer space.
Recently, she's also been called
the Dark Phantom Beast XXX XXX.
As expected.
Ugh.
Impossible.
Withdrew! All but one has withdrew!
Nakamura-san, what is this?
That is not in my data.
Good work.
Dark Phantom Beast.
Looks like you want to be
taken in by my XXX too.
The next event is the Maradong.
All male students, please go to
the sports ground... excuse me.
Please gather at the anal entry gate.
Next is me.
"Mara" means dick, and...
"dong" also means dick.
Of course, it's an erotic contest.
Huh?
Jun.
W-What should I do?
Hey, that's the Invisible XXX Man.
The Unseeable XXX Man!
The only one who
is capable to XXX Katagiri.
Is he planning to use his XXX on us?
Impossible.
It's another full drop out!
Welcome back, Invisible XXX Man.
I'm sorry.
Go! Go!
XXX XXX!
Hooray, hooray, XXX!
Don't lose, don't lose, XXX!
Hooray, hooray, screw screw screw!
An erotic exchange, huh?
To avoid being targeted,
we should cheer too.
Tsk.
As long as I'm alive,
there will come a time
when I have to say lewd words.
Now is that time.
Hooray!
Dick!
Hooray, hooray, dick!
Don't lose, don't lose, dick!
Next is the big pole toppling.
Nakamura-san, how is this event?
This is not in my data.
In this event, pairs of men and women...
will guide their dicks
to the finish line...
and compete on artistic points
in the erotic contest.
Another erotic contest?
I have to expose my lower body
in front of this prisoner surveillance?
But if you don't do it,
they'll get suspicious.
H-However...
It's okay.
I will do my best to make sure
nobody sees your thing.
Heave-ho.
Come on.
Pocky.
With this ripe body, I will participate
in my fourth sport-gasm festival.
Laugh at me as a promiscuous mother.
Shut up, old hag! Don't repeat a year!
The dick, or rather, the referee
will be the second-year Ikuko Onabuta-san.
Not saying "Get pregnant now!"
when you cum...
will become a regulation violation,
so be careful.
Oh, the Hanamaru sisters
are fighting hard over here.
What do you think, Nakamura-san?
That is not in my data.
Come on, come on, you can just cum on me.
Cum, cum!
Don't cum, don't cum!
Don't lose to a younger girl,
you small-fry dick.
Kuh, this little brat.
Here it is!
The Hanamaru Family's direct-transmission
Binaural SCQ Killing Method!
The bratty voice pierces
the crown of the head...
destroys the weak brain
of the shitty small-fry masochist dog!
Hey, even if you fake it,
at least make it stand.
I'm sorry, Nanase.
I...
am impotent.
No way, you're a pure-blooded
onanist, aren't you!?
I can get it up for masturbation.
But when contacts with the opposite sex,
in a situation
with other people watching...
the memory from back then
always comes back.
What's that?
So huge!
How can that fit?
Like a horse's!
The result is this pathetic state.
Jun...
My identity...
the dignity of my dick...
was literally broken at that time.
Now, I'm completely impotent.
At this very moment,
when I absolutely have to get an erection...
How much more
will this dick ruin my life?
Don't look down on me,
Jun.
I am the Legendary XXX, Nanase Katagiri.
Getting one virgin hard
is a piece of cake for me.
Huh?
Hurry up and grope and suck it!
H-However...
What a coward, virgin, impotent!
What did you say?
Ain't you trying too hard?
You are so focused on the boobs.
You virgin.
This provocation.
How lewd!
I don't want to lose!
No, I want to lose!
Loser.
Low income.
Zero life skills.
Leaves the toilet seat up.
Doesn't arrange his shoes at the entrance.
- Wipe the oil from...
- You XXX!
from your hands on your shirt.
Someone who believes a gyaru
who's nice to otaku actually exists.
Is that...
the Binaural SCQ Killing Method!?
She copied the secret technique
of the Haramaki,
passed down since the Sengoku period.
And not just the bratty girl version,
but she even arranged it
into a XXX gyaru version.
This is the Legendary XXX Bitch,
Nanase Katagiri.
Even my data is surprised.
My dick is...
My dick is getting...
Ah...
I can feel a strong
dick aura coming from over here.
Crap, if this keeps up, the FS will notice.
Hey, it's going soft.
Nanase, bring it out,
do it for me.
But...
Even a half-erect is fine, do it!
Alright!
This might be a bit intense.
Get pregnant now!
It's decided!
A facial ejaculation
into a convulsive climax!
Regulation passed!
A magnificent climax!
Even my data is pleased.
Ah.
What? He didn't cum.
Is that Nanase-chan's orgasm?
Too bad.
Referee, what is the verdict?
It certainly looked like he came, but...
the crucial semen is
nowhere to be found, is it?
That's because...
I already drank it all.
1919 points.
As expected of Invisible XXX Man!
The Unseeable XXX Man!
The throbbing-juice XXX Man!
The lewd-juice XXX-XXX!
We managed to trick them, Jun.
Jun?
He's dead.
Nukitashi.
Everyone, thank you for waiting so long.
It is now time for the Seiran Grand Orgy.
Dick dick.
XXX.
When the bell rings.
Here it cums!
The juicy juicy XXX is getting hot.
Make it cums!
Full of energy.
A XXX.
XXX go bang bang.
The night grows late, so behave properly.
Here it cums!
Take out your XXX and fuck a XXX.
Feels good good good.
Cum a bucket, cum a bucket.
Cum a full bucket.
If you want to cum,
you gotta fuck until you moan "An-An."
By the way, the student whose
thing was squeezed out...
in the previous pole toppling
has been taken to the nurse's office.
Everyone, please feel free
to XXX.
It worked.
Asa-chan, execute the plan.
I'm counting on you.
Roger.
No enemies on the way
to the destination.
Took the shortest route.
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
Arrived at the target classroom.
Attempting to enter.
A password huh?
I'm coming, I'm coming.
(1919)
Fap, fap.
(4545)
Bang bang. (8585)
What an elaborate
security system!
Who's there?
Aah!
She slipped past the radar.
What a lack of presence.
I've seen this girl somewhere before...
Um, I...
came to get back what was
confiscated during the bag check.
During the sport-gasm festival?
Is it okay not having lewd sex?
I...
Big brother.
One bogie approaching
from the front.
Crap!
If it's come to this...
What did you just do?
Please, insert this into
the student council's PC.
Huh? This?
Just plug it in.
I'll hold them off.
You don't want to get caught, right?
I-I understand.
Excuse me.
Huh?
It's you.
Weren't you taken
to the nurse's office?
Are you okay now?
Yes, so please have sex with me.
Huh? What are you saying
at a time like this?
Because it's a time like this.
I can have the Disciplinary Committee Director
all to myself!
What?
Sorry, I don't have time
for that now.
I have work in the student council room.
Don't say that.
You don't want to have sex?
What?
Could it be that the rumored...
"Anti-Copulation Force" are actually you?
Huh? N-No, I'm not...
Then let me XXX you!
Wha...
I've said this much XXX
and you won't even show me your nipples.
How could you be so rude?
What do you mean, "set things straight?"
You're the rude one!
Don't you have any respect
for the ordinance?
If you're going to talk like that...
Here.
Are you satisfied with this?
Wow, you're actually showing them?
Huh? What do you want?
Enough, I'm leaving.
Wait!
Damn, I can't let her go yet.
"Dick" wants to be inside you, senpai.
Huh?
What was that just now?
The cry of my dick.
"Dick" wants to be in your pussy, senpai.
Can a dick talk?
And why does it pronoun itself as "dick"?
Is your dick a royalty?
Huh?
A royal dick?
Don't suddenly become sane.
Wait, what do you mean by a royal dick?
Shut up, forget it, don't drag it on.
Answer me!
That's lese majesty!
Don't bring royalty into this.
Alright, I've bought some time
with the royal restoration plan.
Um...
Huh? It's you.
What are you doing here?
What happened to the perverted dance?
I-I got cream-pied too much...
so I came to wash my anal.
I see. So the festival is still going on.
Hurry back to the field.
Ah, yes.
Her movements are clearly strange.
Wait.
Huh?
Crap.
You're hiding something.
The use of props during the
Seiran Grand Orgy is prohibited.
Take off your swimsuit
and spread your legs.
Ah, yes.
Hmm.
No abnormalities detected
by visual inspection.
Were your legs just trembling
from over fucking?
Y-Yes, that's right.
Everyone was so intense.
Then it's fine.
Both of you, hurry back
to the school grounds...
and have a blast climaxing.
Phew.
THE SPORT-GASM FESTIVAL
SURPRISE EJACULATION
Sperm flying under the clear blue sky.
Moans echoing across the island
like a mountain echo.
It was a truly wonderful
sport-gasm festival.
Those who knew the joy of cumming,
and those who knew
the joy of making others cum.
Please use today's experience...
as motivation to strive
for even greater lewdness.
So, where's the memory stick?
Oh, it's in my anal.
Please wait a moment.
Huh?
But just now there was nothing...
I had it tucked away a little deep.
Heave-ho...
I-It was all inside...
Amazing.
No, not at all.
When I got a bishoujo figure
stuck in my ass,
I ended up in the hospital
to get it removed and had anal weakling.
That's amazing.
So, how was it?
The doctor said he never wants
to see a bishoujo figure again.
Not that.
Oh, I plugged it in properly.
But why would you do that?
I...
get incredibly excited when I insert...
my memory stick into a woman's PC.
Oh, I kind of get that.
For real?
Anyway, thank you.
I'm Junnosuke Tachibana,
I just transferred here.
Oh, um... I'm Misaki Hotori.
Nice to meet you, Tachibana-san.
S-So is there...
information on Fumino Kotoyose?
Ahh, I couldn't find it.
I might have to search in a deeper layer.
But you planted the backdoor, right?
Then the information
will increase eventually.
Yeah.
I'm counting on you, Asa-chan.
We have to find Fumino Kotoyose
before the FS does.
Thank goodness.
Neither Fumino-chan nor I were...
recorded as being part
of the Anti-Copulation Force.
I'm sorry.
It was just a matter
of "if I had to choose."
It's okay.
It was a little dangerous, though.
Huh?
I met a cool person.
I hope my first time
can be with someone like that.
Hotori-sama.
I'm just going to masturbate for a bit.
Since I've dragged you into this,
I have something tell you.
Oh, you want to try this?
Not that.
Do you know of a man
named Toshiaki Hitoura?
Hitoura?
Is that...
TOSHIAKI HITOURA
ADVOCATE FOR FREE LEWDNESS
the governor who
created the Perverted Ordinance?
Yes.
My purpose is...
the assassination of that man.
Assassination?
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
I'm glad the sport-gasm festival
ended without any incidents.
Though it would have been perfect if
I could have found my destiny dick.
Now I can resume
the order from the SHO.
The search for Fumino Kotoyose.
Touka-chan, any leads?
The place where the target
is likely to appear next...
is...
The Pervert Land.
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder, have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me